{
    "id": "d5b6a355b63b46dbaf0c277f2e765822",
    "title": "Since and for worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b6d18eaf24d74a50960025186fbfcea2",
            "title": "Since And For Worksheet",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have been waiting for the guests …………….. morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has been suffering from fever ………………. Monday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It has been raining heavily …………….. last night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My father has been serving in the army …………….. 20 years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has not been attending the school ……………… last Monday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been teaching in this college ……………. 10 years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The masons have been building this house ………………. last March.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Man has been struggling against the forces of nature ………………. times immemorial.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A cold breeze has been blowing ……………….. yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has been doing his homework …………… .. 4 o’clock.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}